#### Contact

kelwigrn@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/kellywigington-msn-ccrn-448982b1 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Cardiothorac surgery congenital cardic surgery Heart transplant managment

# Kelly Wigington MSN, CCRN

Critical Care Therapy Specialist for Continuous Renal Replacement Therapy at NxStage Medical, Inc.

Beverly Hills, California

## Summary

I have previously worked for 9 years, as a Cardio-Thoracic surgery ICU Nurse at Cedars Sinai Medical Center, specializing in the management of Cardiogenic shock, CABAG, dissecting aneurysms, and the care of Pre/Post Heart transplantation, in the number one Heart transplant facility in the World. I carry certifications to manage all the devices related to the care of this patient demographic, as well as Congenital Cardiac Surgery management from the neo-nate to adulthood. I am currently participating in Cedars Sinai's pioneer program as an ECMO Nurse Specialist. I am in the process of pursuing my MSN/NP. Concurrently, I am pursuing a passion with changing a persons critical cardiac pathway, and saving lives with Abiomed. I am a clinical educator for the worlds smallest heart pump, the Impella. I assist with educating doctors, Cath labs technicians, and nurses in the insertion and management of the device as well as management and clinical support.

## Experience

NxStage Medical, Inc.

Critical Care Therapy Specialist for Continuous Renal Replacement Therapy

July 2019 - Present (1 year)

Western United States

Cedars-Sinai
Cardiothoracic surgery ICU nurse
September 2009 - Present (10 years 10 months)
Beverly Hills, California

TrialCard
Clinical educator
March 2018 - Present (2 years 4 months)

#### Abiomed

Clinical educator/cunsultant
December 2017 - Present (2 years 7 months)

Greater Los Angeles Area

Clinical educator and consultant for Impella heart pump

Global Skin Care
Director of Asthetics
August 2017 - Present (2 years 11 months)
Santa Monica, California

Nursing Director, overseas and deliver Laser facelift, Botox, Fillers, treatment of problem skin conditions, laser hair removal, spider veil removal

Rodan and Fields Dermatologists
Independent Consultant
December 2015 - Present (4 years 7 months)
Greater Los Angeles Area

Liaison to beautiful youthful skin and financial independence

Contrology Pilates
Owner/ Pilates instructor
January 2005 - Present (15 years 6 months)

Saint johns health center Registered Nurse January 1998 - September 2011 (13 years 9 months)

Beverly Hills center for hyperbaric medicine Director of Nursing services/ Certified Hyperbaric Nurse January 1996 - January 1999 (3 years 1 month)

### Education

Western Governors University

Masters in Nursing, Nursing Education (2017)

The University of Kansas